John and Ginny Dildine collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Sound Recordings
  - AFC 1975/001: SR084, Recorded: 1966-02-26, RXG 0760; 20:42
    4:02 They discuss the previous song. They discuss what Chuck listened to on the radio during his growing up years, the 1930s. They talk about how Chuck got started singing. Dildine asks how Chuck's mother learned her songs. Chuck replies. Dildine asks the Perdues to sing a song Chuck's mother sang.
    7:38 "Three Little Babes" Nan Perdue
    10:30 They discuss the previous song which Nan learned from Chuck's mother. They talk about the music in Nan's family. It was mostly church music. Chuck says that he got the next song from his mother.
    19:46 "Beautiful Isle in the Sea" Chuck and Nan Perdue
    22:10 They discuss the previous song. They talk about collecting songs from Chuck's family and other people. They talk about the education Chuck's parents had and their own college education. They talk about how Chuck and Nan met and their early musical experiences. They talk about "hillbilly" and the negative connotation it had for Nan.
    27:15 Nan reads from a letter from an Aunt. The Aunt is happy and humble that Nan is singing.
    28:45 Dildine asks Chuck why he sings. Chuck responds.
  - AFC 1975/001: SR085, Recorded: 1966-02-26, RXG 0761; 30:15
    This is the second part of a recording for a Dildine radio broadcast. His guests are Chuck and Nan Perdue. The first part of the broadcast is on SR084.
    Start Dildine is speaking with Chuck and Nan Perdue.
    1:28 "Hop along Peter" Chuck and Nan Perdue
    2:49 Dildine and the Perdues discuss the sources from which the Perdues learn their songs.
    4:47 "Coal in the Stone" Chuck and Nan Perdue
    9:50 Dildine and the Perdues discuss the previous song and the song writer. They discuss how Chuck Perdue selects and learns songs. They discuss "what is a folk song?" and "what is ethnic?." The next song is introduced.
    17:14 "Sangaree" [or perhaps "Oh Babe Sangaree"] Chuck and Nan Perdue
    19:12 Dildine and the Perdues discuss the previous song. They introduce the next song.
    20:32 "Only a Miner" Chuck and Nan Perdue
    22:55 Dildine and the Perdues discuss favorite songs. Chuck Perdue says he does not have a single "favorite song," rather he has "perhaps a hundred favorite songs." They discuss what the Perdues sing at home, in private. They introduce the next song.
    26:10 "Song of the Deportees" [a Woody Guthrie song] Chuck and Nan Perdue
    29:28 Dildine closes the broadcast.
    30:15 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR086, Recorded: 1966-02-26, RXG 0762; 17:11
    There is no spoken word in this recording, only 5 songs. Written on the original tape box is "WAMU-FM Folk Music Program October 20, 1966." Also written are: (recorded, October 21, 1966)" and "Michael Cooney." There is nothing in the content of the recording to clarify this. Also, there is no written record of the performers on this tape or the songs they sing.
    Start A man singing a song, a cappella, about a farmer's daughter and a sailor, the title could be "A Sailor Courted a Farmer's Daughter."
    1:55 A man singing and playing guitar. The song may be "He Was a Traveling Man."
    5:45 A man singing a cappella.
    9:15 Man singing and playing banjo.
    13:43 Man singing a cappella. The song may be "John Mitchell is My Name."
  - AFC 1975/001: SR087 (1), Recorded: 1968-08-15 – 1968-08-18, RXG 0763; 1:04:07
    This is side 1 of 2 of a tape recorded at the 1968 Fox hollow Festival. The tape contains only performances. There is no introduction of the performers or songs. The notes which follow are based on a typed list in a folder in the Collection.
    Start "Nonesuch" Faery Ring
    1:25 "Russian Dance" Russell Thomas, flute his son is dancing
    3:45 "The Green hills of Tyrol" George Armstrong, pipes
    6:06 "Good Fish Chowder" Joe Hickerson "while the Dildine puppets dance"
    9:55 "Whistle Daughter Whistle" Toelkins [sounds like a man and a girl singing - father and daughter?]
    11:20 "I'm Gonna Tell" Toelkins [This song was "made up" by Rosalie Sorrels and verses were added by the Toelkins.]
    15:15 "Beauty Song" [Lakota Song] Henry Crowdog, Leonard Crowdog and John Strike
    18:50 "I'm Being Eaten by a Boa Constrictor" Bill Spence
    19:58 Bagpipes, banjo and voices Joe Bossum, Roger and Mrs. Sprung
    26:53 "Sing in the Spring" [a Bruce "Utah" Phillips song] Rosalie Sorrells
    30:45 "I Never Found My Baby" Rosalie Sorrells
    33:55 "My Dearest Dear" Rosalie Sorrells
    38:00 "L'el Bon Vent" [?] [The Good Wind] Bonnie Dodson [in French]
    40:15 "Tumbalalaika" The Aarons [Yiddish folk song]
    44:05 "West Virginia Mine Disaster" Jean Ritchie [Ms. Ritchie wrote his song to give a woman's point of view of the Hominy Falls, West Virginia mine disaster which occurred on May 6, 1968.]
    48:30 "Silicoe" [?] The Penny Whistlers
    52:44 "Dil Mano del Vivero" [?] The Penny Whistlers with Bill Vanaver and Seth Feldman
    55:25 "In the quiet of the Land of Erin" Bonnie Dobson
    58:35 "Meadowlands" Michael Cooney [instrumental on 12 string guitar]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR087 (2), Recorded: 1968-08-15 – 1968-08-18, RXG 0763; 1:02:34
    This is side 2 of 2 of a tape recorded at the 1968 Fox hollow Festival. The tape contains only performances. There is no introduction of the performers or songs. The notes which follow are based on a typed list in a folder in the Collection.
    Start "You Just as Well to Get Ready, You Got to Die" Chuck and Nan Perdue [Perdue said this is a Blind Willie McTell song.]
    3:34 "Fiddle Thing" [Old King Cole type Rabbi] The Aarons, et al [Sung in Yiddish]
    7:58 an unnamed reel Kevin Henry, penny whistle
    9:30 2 unnamed polkas Kevin Henry, wooden flute
    11:08 "Cod Liver Oil" Kevin Henry, a cappella
    12:45 "House Carpenter" Jean Ritchie, vocal and lap dulcimer
    17:00 "What a Goodly Thing" Jean Ritchie, a cappella
    19:57 "Rock Road to Dublin" Owen McBride, a cappella
    22:23 "Dimha Juda" [?] Penny Whistlers
    25:50 unnamed Joe Bossum, bagpipes
    28:55 "Three Ravens" George Britton
    33:05 "Asar Mesuga" [?] Bill Schwarz and Zev Feldman ["Do you remember our childhood?" from North Africa]
    38:15 "Fox Hollow Song" Wilkes and P and SG [?]
    41:15 "Sammy's Bar" Joe Hickerson and Ginny Dildine [written by Cyril Tawney; takes place in Malta; also known as "The Ballad of Sammy's Bar" and "Last Boat A-Leaving"]
    46:41 "Pea Soup Reel" Larry Older, fiddle
    47:53 "A Great Big Sea Hove in Long Beach" Brian Morrison [This song is from Newfoundland]
    50:50 "My Black Rose" Kevin Henry, flute
    52:30 "Dinna Juda" [?] The Pennywhistlers with Bill Vanaver and Zev Feldman
    55:38 "Bonnie James Campbell" George and Gerry Armstrong [this song is from the family of Frank Proffitt]
    57:45 "Greenland Whale" The Toelkins
    1:02:03 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR088 (1), Recorded: 1968-08-15 – 1969-08-18, 1969-08-07 – 1969-08-10, RXG 0764; 1:02:04
    This is side 1 of 2 of a tape recorded at the 1968 and 1969 Fox Hollow Festivals. The 1969 Festival begins at time 36:38. The tape contains only performances. There is no introduction of the performers or songs. The notes which follow are based on a typed list in a folder in the Collection.
    Start West Indian Dancers from Toronto
    5:30 "Ya Vog Gala" (Turkish) Bill Vanever and Zev Feldman
    9:30 "Whooping Bride's Song" Pennywhistlers
    11:42 "Nish Cabana" Pennywhistlers, Bill Vanever and Zev Feldman
    15:02 "Dumbarton Drums" Beers Family
    18:55 "Fox hollow Song" P&SG [The performers are otherwise not identified. One of the performers says he was inspired and wrote the song at the festival. I found the lyrics to this song via Google. It is attributed to Richard Wilkie. Steve Gillette appeared at this Festival. Perhaps he is the SG shown in the collection notes.]
    22:35 "Waiting Tonight" The Toelkins
    26:46 "Golden Ring Around My Susan Girl" The Golden Ring
    29:05 "Molly Hare" The Canterbury Orchestra
    31:17 "Swallow's Tail Reel" Kevin Henry, flute plus fiddle and piano
    32:34 "Will the Circle Be Unbroken" Chuck and Nan Perdue
    35:25 pipes in the distance George Armstrong, bagpipes
    36:38 Close of the 1968 Festival
    36:45 Start of the 1969 Festival
    36:45 "You Can't make a Turtle Come Out" Susan and Becky Boyer and Carol Baker
    38:35 "Alice" Susan and Becky Boyer and Carol Baker, a cappella
    39:18 "The Boys of Blue Hill" Don Lindsay and Bill Drennen, bagpipe duet
    40:47 "Which Way to East Vasselboro" Marshall Dodge, spoken word
    42:48 "Study in Counterpoint" Howard Mitchell, dulcimer
    45:20 "The Thinnest Man" Joe Hickerson
    46:51 "Woad" Joe Hickerson
    49:18 "Gold Watch and Chain" Sweet Corn
    50:52 "Wade in the Water" Joe Hickerson and the Wet Ones
    56:12 "Lord Randall" [three melodies] Tom Kines
    1:02:04 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR088 (2), Recorded: 1968-08-15 – 1969-08-18, 1969-08-07 – 1969-08-10, RXG 0764; 1:05:12
    This is side 2 of 2 of a tape recorded at the 1968 and 1969 Fox Hollow Festivals. No documentation is available for this side of the tape. This side is probably of the 1969 Festival. It contains only performances. There is no introduction of the performers or the songs.
    Start "I'm Gonna Tell" [Joe Hickerson and children?]
    2:02 "Darcy Farrow" Steve Gillette (written by Gillette and Tom Campbell)
    6:03 "Black Waters" [Jean Ritchie?]
    10:32 "MacCrimmon's Lament" [Jean Ritchie? with Kevin Henry? playing bagpipes]
    18:27 "The Musicians" [in Yiddish] Bob Beers, Mimi Samuelson, Betty Needleman and others [the Aarons?]
    23:03 Song and performers are not identified [sounds like a harp; played by a man]
    26:22 Spoken word Man with a Scottish or Irish accent
    26:59 "One Dew" woman singing and guitar
    26:59 "Morning Dew" (first line is: "Take me for a walk in the morning dew") Bonnie Dobson
    31:13 first line is: "You can plant a watermelon up above my grave and let the juice sing through" [Michael Cooney?]
    31:45 song not identified performer not identified [sounds like a wooden flute]
    34:55 "McPherson's Lament," "Putty Up the Nail Holes," "The 8th of January" (three fiddle tunes) [Sam Hinton] on the banjo
    39:52 Lead Belly's version of a song he called "Red Cross Door" unidentified man singing with 12 string guitar
    44:05 A Joseph Able Trivett song, recorded by Sandy Patton "Go Away from Me Young Man" [several versions of this song have been recorded as "The Cuckoo is a Pretty Bird"] Introduction by a man, sung a cappella by a woman
    48:15 unidentified song [it seems to be a version of a traditional song called "Coulter's Candy"] sung by several unidentified women
    50:10 unidentified song sung by several unidentified women
    52:50 unidentified song [Canterbury Orchestra?]
    54:32 "Swipesy Cakewalk," a Scott Joplin tune unidentified man playing 12 string guitar
    57:35 "The Honest John Quadrille" [Canterbury Orchestra?]
    1:01:55 "Old Joe Clark" and other tunes [Canterbury Orchestra?]
    1:05:13 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR089 (1), Recorded: 1969-08-07 – 1969-08-10, RXG 0765; 1:03:34
    This is side 1 of 2 of a tape recorded at the 1969 Fox Hollow Festival. It contains only performances; there is no introduction of the performers or the songs. The notes which follow are based on a typed list in a folder in the Collection.
    Start "Eileen Aroon" Jean Redpath
    4:53 "Oh Brethren, Ain't She Happy" Lynn Burnstine, and Jane Munson, with dulcimer
    6:38 "Come Life, Shaker Life" Lynn Burnstine, and Jane Munson, with dulcimer
    8:04 "Cotton Needs a Pickin So Bad" Dan Smith, with Bessie Jones, Mike Rivers (guitar) and Andy Wallace (banjo)
    11:43 "Pleasant and Delightful" Louis Killen
    15:23 "It's Hard to Love another Woman's Man" Barbara Carns, with Dennis Coggs, Don Odette and Bill Schwarz
    18:52 Don Burnstine introduces the Fox Hollow Electric Rock (and Roll) Band Michael Cooney, Bill Spence, Billy Schwarz and [Eldrin Fenig?]
    21:17 "I'm a Rover" Owen McBride
    27:10 "Old dun Cow" Owen McBride
    31:32 "Boil that Cabbage Down" Grant Rader, with piano, guitar and bass
    33:02 "The Old Granite State" Tony and Irene Saletan
    36:02 "Bright Morning Stars" Tony and Irene Saletan, a cappella
    38:53 "Oh Mary, Don't You Weep" Jim McGowen
    43:53 "I Wish They'd Do It Now" Michael Cooney
    48:17 Bulgarian gate knocking song The Pennywhistlers
    50:33 "How Can I Keep From Singing" The Pennywhistlers
    56:18 "What You Gonna Do When Death Come Creepin in the Room?" Tom Winslow
    59:30 "Rake and Rambling Boy" Tony and Irene Saletan
    1:03:34 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR089 (2), Recorded: 1969-08-07 – 1969-08-10, RXG 0765; 57:03
    This is side 2 of 2 of a tape recorded at the 1969 Fox Hollow Festival. It contains only performances; there is no introduction of the performers or the songs. The notes which follow are based on a typed list in a folder in the Collection.
    Start "Glory Hallelujah, Praise His Name" Tony and Irene Saletan
    5:24 "Shto E Milo" The Pennywhistlers and Louis Killen
    8:50 "Rocky Road to Dublin" Kevin Henry, bag pipes
    10:35 "Shady Grove" Mike Seeger, banjo
    13:00 "Greenland Bound" [a whaling song] Louis Killen, concertina
    16:25 "The Wind That Shook the Barley" Jean Redpath, a cappella
    20:29 "If I Were Free to Speak My Mind" Ed Trickett with Penny and Henry Tufts
    24:42 "Buck Dancer's Choice" Howie Mitchell, Appalachian dulcimer
    26:48 ["Kuafu"] [mid Vietnamese widows lament] Steve Addiss, played on a 16 string Vietnamese instrument call a [tran]
    29:45 "I Know You Belong to Everybody But You Can't Deny That I'm You" Steve and Mary Addiss
    34:41 "You Can't Get There From Here," etc. Marshall Dodge, spoken word
    50:01 ["Go to Sleep"] or perhaps ["My Precious One'] Guy MacKenzie
    53:55 "God's Not Dead" Bessie Jones
    57:02 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR090, Recorded: 1969-08, RXG 0761; 31:11
    The notes on the tape box in the collection file say this was recorded Sunday afternoon at the 1969 Fox Hollow Festival. The first four songs are by the Armstrong Family, George, Gerry and their two daughters Rebecca and Jennifer. The second part of the tape is by Louis Killen. It is continued on SR091.
    Start "Hard Time Cotton Mill Girls" The Armstrong Family
    2:05 "A Man of Words" The Armstrong Family
    5:27 "The Mist Covered Mountain" The Armstrong Family, instrumental: George, bag pipe chanter; Gerry, guitar; Children, fiddles
    7:37 "At the Foot of Yonder Mountain" The Armstrong Family
    10:39 Louis Killen is introduced
    10:55 "The Flying Cloud" Louis Killen, a cappella
    18:44 "Greenland Bound" Louis Killen, vocal and concertina
    21:56 Louis Killen tells a story of "the fox changing"
    30:15 unidentified song about Mr. Fox Louis Killen, a cappella
    32:11 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR091, Recorded: 1969-08, RXG 0761; 32:46
    This is a continuation of SR090.
    Start Lou Killen discusses the next song.
    0:55 "The Little Red Fox" and other tunes instrumental, Killen, concertina
    5:26 "The Kielder Hunt" Killen, a cappella
    12:00 Lost item announcement
    12:14 Discussion of "Lady Chatterly's Lover" unidentified woman with British or Scottish accent; may be Jean Redpath
    14:10 "Our Old Cat Died Last Night" [Redpath]
    17:53 "The Wind that Shakes the Barley" [Redpath]
    22:25 Medley of children's game songs [Redpath]
    23:45 "Ye Cannae Shove Ye Granny Aff the Bus" [Redpath]
    24:54 "The Store" [Redpath]
    26:42 An unidentified Robert Burns love song [Redpath]
    29:20 "Wild Mountain Thyme" [Redpath]
    32:46 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR092, Recorded: 1969-05-03, RXG 0813; [no tape log is available for this item]
    Jerry Sharp, Topic Records
  - AFC 1975/001: SR093, Recorded: 1969-05-03, RXG 0814; [no tape log is available for this item]
    [Jerry] Sharp interview, #2.
  - AFC 1975/001: SR094, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0768; 12:51
    This SR contains three copies of the same field recording. According to Todd Harvey of the American Folklife Center, this is "Bright Morning Stars Are Rising," by G.D. Vowell, collected in 1937 by Alan and Elizabeth Lomax.
    Start "Bright Morning Stars are Arising" G.D. Vowell
    2:20 "Bright Morning Stars are Arising" G.D. Vowell and others
    4:30 First repeat of above.
    8:40 Second repeat of above.
    12:51 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR095, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0769; 31:32
    See SR094. This SR contains several copies of the same field recording. According to Todd Harvey of the American Folklife Center, this is "Bright Morning Stars Are Rising," by G.D. Vowell, collected in 1937 by Alan and Elizabeth Lomax.
  - AFC 1975/001: SR096, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0770; 36:04
  - AFC 1975/001: SR097, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0771; 26:38
  - AFC 1975/001: SR098, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0772; 26:38
  - AFC 1975/001: SR099, Recorded: undated, RXG 0815; [no tape log is available for this item]
    [Tape Box is labeled "LWO 16797 / R52 B1"]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR0100, Recorded: undated, RXG 0816; [no tape log is available for this item]
    [Tape Box is labeled "LWO 16797 / R52 B2"]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR101 (1), Recorded: probably 1969 or 1970, RXG 0773; 01:01:11
    This seems be a recording of a concert by John and Ginny Dildine and guests. One of the guests is Joe Hickerson.
    Start "Working on the New Railroad" Joe Hickerson and others, guitar
    7:33 John Dildine speaking. An unidentified woman introduces a song written by Rosalie Sorrells. The Tolkien, family from Oregon, has added two verses.
    8:49 "I'm Gonna Tell" unidentified woman and others, banjo
    11:21 John Dildine speaking. An unidentified man introduces a railroad song.
    12:12 "The Dummy Line" unidentified man, guitar
    16:37 Unidentified woman introduces the next song which she learned in summer camp.
    17:15 "My Father Killed a Kangaroo" unidentified woman and others, a cappella, also done as a round
    25:01 Getting ready for the next song
    25:41 The Cow Puncher" [The singer says this song was written by Jenny Haley] [Joe Hickerson?], guitar
    29:35 Getting ready for the next song. An unidentified woman introduces the next song.
    30:21 "Those Good Peanuts" unidentified man and woman, guitar
    33:55 Introduction to the next song
    35:04 "Garbage" [Joe Hickerson] and other, guitar
    38:50 An unidentified woman introduces the next song.
    39:20 "Don't Throw Your Junk in My Back Yard" unidentified woman and other, a cappella, sung as a round
    44:00 John Dildine introduces the next song. It is a McPeak family song which he learned from Francis McPeak.
    45:06 "Monaghan Fair" John Dildine, a capella
    47:43 Introduction to the next song.
    48:27 "Three Jolly Rogues of Lynn" Joe Hickerson, guitar
    50:10 Getting ready for the next song
    51:45 "À La Volette" [The first line is "Once there was a swallow and her birdies three"] two unidentified woman, guitar
    54:54 Introduction to the next song [Ginny Dildine?]
    56:36 "Old Babbum and the Boar" [Ginny Dildine?], guitar
    1:01:11 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR101 (2), Recorded: probably 1969 or 1970, RXG 0773; 34:32
    Start "Fiddler's Green" Joe Hickerson and others, guitar
    4:15 John Dildine talks about working with marionettes.
    6:10 "Who Killed Cock Robin" Ginny Dildine, guitar
    12:07 Preparation for the next song
    12:58 "Charlie" Joe Hickerson and others, guitar
    17:38 John Dildine makes and announcement. He introduces next week's program. He asks for volunteers to "dance a puppet."
    22:25 ["It's Nearly Sundown"] Joe Hickerson, guitar
    27:22 Preparation for and introduction of the next song.
    28:45 "Going Down the Valley" unidentified man and others, guitar
    34:01 End of song
    34:32 End of recording
  - AFC 1975/001: SR0102, Recorded: undated, RXG 0817; [no tape log is available for this item]
    [Tape box is labeled "Bulgarian Folk Instruments. Narrator tells about various instruments."]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR103, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0774; 24:42
    This is a recording of a John Dildine radio broadcast with Ellen and Robin Christenson. It was recorded in the home of Peter and Judy Weston. See also SR062 and SR068
    Start "Little Birdie" Ellen and Robin Christenson, banjo and guitar
    4:19 Dildine speaks with Ellen and Robin Christenson.
    9:09 "I'm a Poor Country Boy" Robin Christenson, banjo
    12:00 Dildine speaks with Ellen and Robin Christenson.
    15:27 Ellen and Robin Christenson, banjo and guitar
    16:58 Dildine does a station break. He speaks with Ellen Christenson.
    18:20 "One Morning in May" Ellen Christenson, guitar
    21:16 Dildine asks for another song.
    22:14 ["Sangarie?"] Ellen and Robin Christenson, banjo and guitar.
  - AFC 1975/001: SR104, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0775; 13:02
    This recording contains a number of "takes" of different songs by an unidentified man and woman. They may be Chris and Pixie Christy. There is guitar accompaniment. See SR003.
    Start "First He Made the Sun" (take 1) unidentified man and woman, guitar
    1:44 "Katie Dear" (take 1) unidentified man and woman, guitar
    3:50 "Katie Dear" (more) unidentified man and woman, guitar
    4:35 [nothing useful]
    5:17 "Ain't Got No Place to Lay My Head" (take 1) unidentified man and woman, guitar
    7:10 "Ain't Got No Place to Lay My Head" (take 2) unidentified man and woman, guitar
    9:06 [nothing useful]
    9:40 "When Are You Comin' to See Me" (take 1) unidentified man and woman,
    11:15 "When Are You Comin' to See Me" (take 2) unidentified man and woman,
    13:02 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR105, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0776; 14:15
    This is a recording of seven songs of sailors and the sea. The performer is not identified
    Start "Pretty Susan" ("The Pride of Kildare") unidentified man, guitar
    2:16 "Bound for the Rio Grande" unidentified man, guitar
    4:32 "What Shall We Do with the Drunken Sailor" unidentified man, guitar
    6:01 "The Lass of Mohea" unidentified man, guitar
    8:20 ["Tin Swanky Pot?"] unidentified man, guitar
    10:21 "Hanging Johnny" unidentified man, guitar
    12:02 The first line is: "I thought I heard the old man say "good bye fare you well, good bye fare you well"" unidentified man, guitar
    14:15 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR0106, Recorded: undated, RXG 0817; [no tape log is available for this item]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR107 (1), Recorded: unknown, RXG 0777; 20:31
    This is a recording of six songs by an unidentified woman accompanied by a band.
    0:21 "Ain't Nobody's Business" unidentified woman and band
    2:31 Abilene" unidentified woman and band
    7:00 "Frankie and Johnny" unidentified woman and band
    10:39 "Copper Kettle" unidentified woman and band
    14:11 "We Are Crossing the River Jordan" unidentified woman and band
    16:47 "Trouble in Mind" unidentified woman and band
    20:13 End of recording
    20:31 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR108 (1), Recorded: unknown, RXG 0778; 15:01
    This appears to be the making of a demo of two (unidentified) women singers with banjo, guitar and bass. An unidentified male performer is also on the recording. It is continued on SR108 (3).
    Start Talking and false starts of a song.
    0:42 Take 1 of a song with the first line: "If he's gone, let him go, let him sink or let him swim"
    2:51 Performers talking
    3:12 Take 2 of the previous song
    3:40 Performers talking
    4:09 Take 3 of the previous song
    6:34 When I First Came Unto this Country"
    9:46 Performers talking and tuning
    10:15 Take 1 "Jack-A-Roe"
    10:48 Performers talking about the lyrics of the song
    11:30 Jack-A-Roe"
    6:22 "The Cruel War"
  - AFC 1975/001: SR108 (2), Recorded: unknown, RXG 0778; 1:33